[{"answer": "Well, look, there's certainly people who support Mubarak.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 39, "question": "I mean, what are you picking up here?", "qSentId": 38}, {"answer": "Well, it's the first time that I felt threatened by sort of a mob, you know, walking my way.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "What was it like for to you go through that?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about right now.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "What is wrong with doing that?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "Oh, I agree that he's a dictator.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Rudy, isn't the problem, though -- I mean do you agree that he is a dictator?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Hopefully we've done that.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 186, "question": "You cannot have six months of these protests on the streets?", "qSentId": 185}, {"answer": "Well, I think -- I think Israel has to do the same thing the United States does, which is it has to talk to Mubarak about as quickly as possibly -- as possible selecting somebody, a general or a group of generals, who can run an interim government, and also bring in, if they can, as they do that, people from civilian life, people from the protesters, but not the Brotherhood.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What would you do if you are now able to have any influence over this to protect Israel?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "They're now war correspondents.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "What are you thinking when you see that?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Presumably it's because they're bringing the wrong message to the world which is that Mubarak's thugs, and I have to assume they're ordered by him or his people, they are trying to get rid of these protest, something, trying to stop this.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Why is this being done?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Well, let me -- let try, you know, I'm hardly going to be the spokesperson for Mubarak.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "What I don't understand is why President Obama isn't coming out now and stopping more bloodshed effectively by saying that's it, enough?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "I think what he is doing is sending his emissary, Frank Wisner, who is a very --", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "What should you do, do you think?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "What some people have said is you have to think of what's in the best national interest of the United States.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "How many times can America go to war, say, with someone like Saddam Hussein and with Britain, by the way, calling him a dictator that treats his men badly while propping up people like Mubarak?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Very dramatic.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "I want to discuss now an extraordinary event in your life when very recently you discovered that you needed open heart surgery, which is a pretty dramatic thing to discover, isn't it?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "Whatever it is in their makeup -- women think that the biggest problem for them will be breast cancer.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Why more women than men?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "You did.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Did I say that?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Ace Hardware.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Where did they get the new arteries from?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "In my private life, I'm not such a tough cookie.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "That moment when you knew that you had this big problem, and that you could potentially die if you didn't have the surgery, even for a tough cookie like you, what was going through your mind then?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "I'm going to talk to you about this when we come back.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 435, "question": "Have you had an EKG?", "qSentId": 434}, {"answer": "Ivan, thank you for that report.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Piers?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "Well, the pictures are horrific, so you're interested just watching it.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "How interested should they be?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Could you imagine never going on television again?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 494, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 493}, {"answer": "Well, probably not as entertaining as yours has been, Barbara.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Do you have a private life?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Well, I think I'll know when it's time to go.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "How long are you going to go on for?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "You can't do that.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "What's been the single greatest interview?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "You are?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "He was also in a very difficult position.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "What would he have made of what's going on in his country?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "I have this little dog --", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 558, "question": "Who has been the love of your life?", "qSentId": 557}, {"answer": "If I had five minutes to live, I would be with my daughter and closest friends.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "I've had a lot of special really very men in my life.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 567, "question": "Are you still on the dating scene?", "qSentId": 566}, {"answer": "I think the years in the Middle East.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "But what would be the moment in your career, other than the Sadat, which is a great interview -- what would be the one moment in your career you would relive?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "There are people -- the Pope has never been interviewed.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "But who's the person you never interviewed you wished you had?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "I mean, 60 years of amazing secrets.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "Wouldn't you like to do an interview with her?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "Yes, I have.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "Have you met Camilla?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Not enormously, no.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 620, "question": "Are you excited about the royal wedding?", "qSentId": 619}, {"answer": "I'm taking my whole show there for a week.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "Do you?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "How early I have to get up in the morning.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "What is the last thing you think about when you go to bed?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "You know --", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "Do you have any regrets, real regrets?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "Well, we've certainly seen an escalation in the use of force here during the first more than 12 hours of this battle here.", "docId": "110202pmt", "aSentId": 672, "question": "Do you think the death toll may rise?", "qSentId": 671}]